Sooha.
Sooha, can you hear me?
Sooha, are you okay? Are you hurt?
Heli?
Where are you?
I'll come get you.
Um, I'm busy right now.
Huh? Sooha?
Khan!
It's good to see you again.
Uh, um...
He's gone.
He vanished!
- Dark Moon: The Blood Altar -
- Night of the Total Eclipse -
Are you alone, or are you with someone?
Huh? Um...
She's here with me.
You got a problem with that?
Jakah...
It's just the two of you?
No, the others came with—
That's none of your business.
Khan!
Let's race boats!
Hey, it's Sooha!
Good to see...
Sooha! Jakah!
Shion!
Are you two...
Huh?
Sooha.
Heli.
Are you hurt anywhere?
No, I'm fine.
The others saved me.
Hurt? Did something happen?
Some vampires showed up
out of nowhere just now.
What?!
At this hour? And in the plaza?
Where are they now?
We dealt with them.
You don't have to worry about it.
You can't be serious.
We wouldn't have put Sooha
in danger in the first place.
What was that?!
Jaan.
Sooha, don't get too close to these guys.
For your own sake.
Huh?
That's right. You should hang
out with us next weekend.
Sooha already agreed to hang
What? I did?
I see. Then let's meet up
the weekend after that!
Huh?
We have plans that weekend
and every weekend after.
Forever and ever, never-ending!
Quit messing with me, brat!
What was that, idiot?!
Shut up! Takes one to know one!
Anyway, Sooha, we really are throwing
a birthday party three weeks from now.
You'll come, right?
Huh? I-If it's someone's birthday,
I'll definitely be there.
Hey! Don't lie to her!
It's true.
If you don't believe me,
why don't you come, too?
Like hell I'm going!
I'm not celebrating that!
I'm joking. I'd never invite you guys.
I think it'd be nice to
celebrate together.
If Sooha says so, then I'm going for sure.
Me, too. Send me an invitation.
I'd like to go, too.
What?!
I said I was joking!
There's no way I'd ever invite you guys.
What was that?!
We're offering to attend
your boring little party!
That's enough.
You dusty losers aren't invited.
Quit it, guys.
Sooha said she was attacked
by vampires, right?
They put Sooha in danger.
Yeah.
You two seem awfully
concerned about Sooha.
Huh? Oh, yeah. I wonder why.
I sense a strange power in her.
To tell you the truth, so do I.
No!
Sooha's words froze me in place then.
There's something up with her.
Maybe it's related to
today's vampire attack.
Yeah, and that's not all.
They may have been protecting Sooha,
but I'm intrigued that they
fought their own kind.
That person I saw at the plaza today...
If Chris had lived to be an adult,
he definitely would've looked like that.
But I thought Chris was dead.
Sooha.
He definitely called my name back there.
Is Chris actually still alive?
But how?
And why didn't he come see me sooner?
I can't believe he
disappeared right away, too.
No, none of that matters!
I only care that you're still alive!
Chris!
Chris! Chris!
Sooha, I missed you.
You're alive?
Yeah, I am.
Are you really Chris?
Yes, really. This brings back memories.
Anyway, you haven't changed a bit.
Chris...
You really are Chris!
I'm glad to see you again, Sooha.
Chris...
But why?
A dream?
That must've been a dream.
I know.
There's no way Chris will be there.
This is all a dream.
I knew it. He's not here.
Why is it so dark when
there's a full moon tonight?
I'm the only one who
didn't transform again.
Why am I the only one who can't?
Everyone else naturally becomes a wolf
under the light of the full moon,
so why not me?
Am I defective after all?
Sooha?
Khan?
Khan.
What are you doing here at this hour?
And in pajamas?
Huh? What?
He seems different from usual.
I-I was in such a hurry, I didn't change!
D-Don't worry about it.
It happens when you're rushing.
Heck, it happens to me all the time.
What? All the time?
A-Anyway, what are you doing here?
Huh?
Oh, um... I-I just wanted
to see the ocean at night.
By yourself?
Yeah. I thought there was
a full moon tonight.
It's a total eclipse.
When the Sun, Earth, and Moon line up,
the Moon is hidden in the Earth's shadow.
It's a really special day.
Yeah. I learned about it,
but this is my first time seeing it.
By the way...
What are you doing here at this hour?
I... came to see the total eclipse.
I see.
By yourself? Where are the others?
It's just me. They're...
asleep.
L-Listen, Sooha. Want me to walk you back?
Huh?
Some vampires showed up
today, right? I'm worried.
Are you sure? Thanks.
I was actually a little scared.
About the vampires,
and about the stray dogs, too.
Stray dogs?
Yeah. Didn't you hear
them howling just now?
W-Were they?
I hope they don't attack people.
They don't! Especially not wolves.
What?
Uh, I mean...
They're, uh... surprisingly kind animals.
That's true. Plus, wolves are cool.
What? You really think so?
You like wolves, too?
Yeah! At least, I like seeing them on TV.
But I'd be scared if I ran into one.
I see.
W-Well, I'll walk you back.
Okay. Thanks.
- Dark Moon: The Blood Altar -
Jino, do you have any plans for today?
Not really.
How do you feel?
Normal?
Stare...
You want me to practice shooting
with you, right? I know.
You never stop throwing balls around.
Hey.
Huh? He's not with you?
Well, Shion said...
Shion.
I'm so tired.
What's up?
I didn't get to see Sooha.
Oh, right. The birthday party.
There's no rush.
You'll see her eventually, right?
I couldn't wait to give this to her.
I wore myself out looking
everywhere for her.
Yes, yes. That must've been hard for you.
Since you're so tired,
I'll give this to Sooha for you.
Hey.
Don't, Jaan.
I'll give it to her.
Jino?
If you're gonna fight, I'll do it.
Noa?
I'm concerned about your
ability to deliver the invite.
Maybe I should do it.
You too, Jakah?!
Here.
Honestly, guys!
Sorry.
Sorry, sorry.
It's strange, isn't it?
Before we met Sooha, we always
wanted to keep to ourselves.
You're right.
We'd never thought about
inviting someone else.
I'm excited for the party.
All the more reason to make
sure she gets the invitation.
I know.
I think I know where Sooha might be.
Sooha.
Heli.
Here to borrow some books?
Yeah. What about you?
I'm returning a book today.
That's the book from the other day.
Yeah. I finished it.
Was it interesting?
Yeah. It's on legends from
an ancient kingdom.
There are vampires and werewolves in them.
Vampires and werewolves...
They're famous for being
ancient mortal enemies.
They often appear together.
I see.
Werewolves turn into wolves
during the full moon, right?
That's right.
Come to think of it, there was
a total eclipse yesterday.
Yeah.
Maybe they can't transform during a full
moon if a total eclipse conceals it.
I'm not sure.
But apparently, werewolves fall in love
with the first woman they
see during a total eclipse,
and will love that woman alone
for the rest of their life.
That sounds lovely.
But eclipses are rare.
I doubt they fall in love that way often.
That's true. Did you see the eclipse?
No. I was asleep.
Did you?
Yeah, at the inlet.
What? You went to
the inlet after that? Why?
I just wanted to see the ocean at night.
I thought there was a full moon last night
and was surprised by how dark it was,
and then Khan told me
about the total eclipse.
We happened to meet by the sea.
You met Khan on the night
of a total eclipse?
Yeah. What about it?
Oh, it's nothing.
Invite me next time.
Okay.
A shadow crossed his face for a moment.
Did he not like that I met up with Khan?
I like looking at the sea at night, too.
Really?
Come to think of it, I wonder
why they don't get along.
Is it because they attend rival schools?
They said they compete for the
nightball championship every year.
Maybe they're on edge since
they have a game coming up.
Well, that can't be helped.
Anyway, yesterday must've been tough.
Huh? Oh, yeah.
Let me know right away if
anything unusual happens, okay?
This wasn't just a coincidence.
They were targeting Sooha.
Okay. I'm fine, though.
So, have you gotten used to school?
Yeah. For the first time in my life,
I think I'm having fun at school.
I see.
All because of you, Heli. Thank you.
You don't need to thank me.
I'm just glad you're having fun.
But you're the reason I made friends with—
Sooha.
Jino.
So you were at the library after all.
Are you both borrowing books?
Yeah. Heli's returning one, actually.
Ah, I see.
Are you all borrowing books, too?
Of course we are. Reading's my hobby.
I came to borrow a book
on quantum mechanics.
I've been interested in it lately.
Stop lying, you two.
Noa, your book's upside down.
We just thought you'd be here, Sooha.
Aside from Heli,
none of us really read much.
Don't tell her that.
I read three whole lines.
So, what were you talking about?
I was asking Heli about the book he read.
He said it was about an ancient kingdom.
There are werewolves and
vampires in the stories.
Werewolves?
Yeah. Heli told me about
a romantic werewolf legend.
What legend?
During a total eclipse, werewolves fall
in love with the first woman they see.
They love her and only her forever.
Isn't that so romantic?
Oh, please.
Maybe so, but werewolves are just mutts.
Yeah. You have to deal with the
shedding whenever they're around.
And you'll never stop sneezing.
They say they're part-human and part-wolf,
but they're less than 10% human.
Yeah.
Oh, Solon? You're here?
Y-Yeah. Anyone who's half-stray dog
is savage, stupid, and crude.
Now, now. No need to go that far.
Sooha thinks the werewolf
legend is romantic.
About them falling in love with the first
person they see during a total eclipse?
That's just werewolves being stupid.
Vampires are far... better.
But...
Vampires don't feel any love at all.
No, they don't even have
the kind heart of a human.
Just yesterday, they suddenly attacked me!
And... and...
they kill innocent people
and turn them into vampires!
So there's no way they
even know what love is.
Vampires are just cold, brutal monsters!
Werewolves are way better!
No, you can't even compare them.
Vampires are the worst!
S-Sorry for flipping out so suddenly.
I-It's fine.
We shouldn't have said
those things to begin with.
Y-Yeah.
You have nothing to apologize for, Sooha.
Yeah.
Everyone has their own preferences.
I just really hate vampires.
Yeah.
We know. Everyone hates vampires.
I see. Her friend was killed by a vampire.
Yeah. That's why she hates them so much.
That's not all.
You know that incredible power she has?
You mean her super strength?
She's been mistaken for
a vampire because of it.
She's probably suffered a lot for it.
Then what are we supposed to do?
I couldn't give this to her.
Not even you could do it?
What? I know how to read a room, okay?
Maybe we can't invite her
to our birthday party.
I thought there was a full moon last night
and was surprised by how dark it was,
and then Khan told me
about the total eclipse.
I finally found you.
Next time, Episode 5:
"Waxing Moon: Bite My Neck."
- Bite My Neck -